Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation; Records apap313
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1994-2005, Undated; 2; 3.2 cubic ft.
  Series 2 contains the internal and external communications of Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation. These communications deal with administrative and committee work, finances, donor relations, event planning, outreach, victim support, and prisoner experiences. Along with the letters and memos sent by the organizations' members, this series also contains handwritten notes, newspaper clippings, floppy disks, zip disks, cassettes, dvds, and MVFR publications as well as correspondence that Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation received. When present, file names assigned by the organization were preserved.
  - "1000 Voices Against the New Jersey Death Penalty", 1996 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Administation, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Audit Findings, 2002 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Banner, 2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Bessie's Fund, 1995; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Board Members, 1994-1998; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Case Statement on Approach to Abolition, Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Checks Paid, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Citizens Against the Death Penalty, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Committees, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Concert Updates, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Conference Handout, 2001 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Contribution Thank Yous (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Contribution Thank Yous (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Contribution Thank Yous, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Contribution Thank Yous (1 of 3), 1997 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Contribution Thank Yous (2 of 3), 1997 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Contribution Thank Yous (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Contribution Thank Yous, 1997 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Thank Yous, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Contributions, 1994-1995; 1997; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - "A Coordinated Plan to Abolish the Illinois Death Penalty", 2000 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Floppy-disk 24)
  - Cover Letter and Assessment Questionaire, 1999 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Cover Sheets for Healing the Wounds of Murder, Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Cushing, Renny, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Dead Man Walking, 1995-1998; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Dead Man Walking - Alan Ames and Associates, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Dead Man Walking - Concert Invitations, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Dead Man Walking - HAVOC (Tim Robbins), 1995; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Dead Man Walking - Poster Auction, Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Dead Man Walking - Requests for Information, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Dean, Robert, 2002 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - "Dignity Denied", 2002; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Dora B. Schriro V. Warren Wesley Summerlin, 2004 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - European Parliament, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Email Contact Information for Anti-Death Penalty Groups Member, Undated (Floppy-disk 25)
  - Execution of Gary Davis, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Family Members, 1992-1999 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Feingold, Ross, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Finances and Donations, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Financial Audit, 2002; 2004 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - General Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - General Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - General Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Harris, Elinda, 2005 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Herman, Susan, 2001 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - "Hidden Victims" Proposal, 2003; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Hines, Maria, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Information for Audit, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Invitations to Healing the Wounds of Murder, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Journey of Hope California, 1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Journey of Hope Name, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Contribution Thank Yous (A-E), 1996 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Contribution Thank Yous (F-K), 1996 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Contribution Thank Yous (L-R), 1996 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Contribution Thank Yous (S-Z), 1996 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Contribution, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Fundraising, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Invitations, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Mailing List, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Meetings, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Speaking Engagements, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Juvenile Exhibit, 2004; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Kambule, Azi - Mississippi, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Letter to Nebraska ACLU Affiliate, Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Lifelines Conference, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Lucero, Bill, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Lifers Group-Massachusetts Prison, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Mail List MDB (February 25th), 1999 (Floppy-disk 26)
  - Mailing List Exchange, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Mailing List Member-Change of Address and Requests for Information, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Mailing List-Removal, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Maine Death Penalty Rejected, 1999 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - McAdams, Brian, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Members, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Michigan Prison Creative Arts Project, 1998; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Missouri State Public Defender, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - MVFR Committees, 1997; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - MVFR Membership, 1991-2000; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - MVFR Website, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1994; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Navaho Death Penalty, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Negative Response to MVFR, 1999-2001 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Negative Response to Parade Magazine Article, 1998; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Negative Responses to Parade Magazine Article, 1998 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - New Hampshire Death Penalty Abolition, 2000-2003 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - New Office, 1998; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - New York Times Ad, 1999; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - "Not In Our Name" Exhibit, 2004; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - "Not In Our Name" - Participants, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - November National Leadership Forum, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Oklahoma Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1995; 1997; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Oregon March Against the Myth, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Outlook (January 27th), 1998 (Cassette 2)
  - "Outside In" - Documentary, Undated (Dvd 1)
  - "Outside In" Documentary, Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Peace Studies, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - People of Faith Against the Death Penalty, 1994-1995; 1997; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Post, June, 2005 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Prisoner Letters, 1996; 1999-2001; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Program Ideas, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Publications, 1994; 2000; Undated (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Racial Diversity, 1998; 2001 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Requests for Government Proclamations, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Requests for Information, 1996-1997; 1999-2001; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Requests for Information after article in "Parade" (A-K), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Requests for Information after article in "Parade" (L-S), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Requests for Information after article in "Parade" (T-Z), 1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Requests for Speakers, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Response to "Dignity Denied", 2002; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Response to Prisoner Letters, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Responses to Request for Information after "Parade" article, 1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Restorative Justice Conference, 1999; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Ross, Michael, 1995-1997; 1999; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Ross, Michael, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Scotland Law Program-Pat Lucie, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - State Action - Iowa, 1995; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - State Govenors, 1996-1997; 1999-2000 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Student Death Penalty Conference, 2003 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Support for European Parliament Resolution, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Tariq Khamisa Foundation, 2000 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Texas Chapter, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - United Kingdom Chapter, 1996-1998 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - United Nations - Human Rights, 1997; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Victim's Rights Amendment, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Virginia Senate, 1997 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - "The Voice", 1994-1996; 2003; Undated (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - "Waiting Room", 2001 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Website Suggestion, Undated (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - West Winfield Speaking Engagement, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
- Outreach and Publications, 1994-2004, Undated; 3; 1.2 cubic ft.
  Aranged Alphabetically.
  The outreach and publications series presents materials that Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation and its members created in an attempt to spread the word about their fight to end the death penalty. To spread word about their cause, the organization and its members created exhibits and books, wrote articles and newsletters, gave speeches, and attempted to create adult education classes. Contained in this series are correspondence, newspaper clippings, newsletters, brochures, booklets, manuscripts, transcripts, reports, drafts, proofs, schedules, floppy disks, zip disks, dvds, and vhs tapes.
  - American Friends Service Committee Bus and Train Advertising Campaign, 1999; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 1)
  - Amnesty Bow Article on Renny Cushing and Murder Victims' Familes for Reconciliation, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 2)
  - "Beyond the News: Murder Close Up", 1995 (Vhs 1)
  - Brochures, 1997; 2001; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 3)
  - Business Cards and Fundraising Letter, 1999 March; Undated (Floppy-disk 27)
  - Cushing, Renny - Pictures, Undated (Floppy-disk 28)
  - Cushing, Renny - Speeches and Articles, Undated (Floppy-disk 29)
  - "Dignity Denied", 2002 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 4)
  - Educational Resources, 2000-2004 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 5)
  - Fall 2005 Newsletter Development, Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 6)
  - "Families of Victims Murdered by Juveniles Oppose Juvenile Executions", Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Letter, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 8)
  - History of Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation, Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 9)
  - Juvenile Exhibit - List of Damages, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 10)
  - Juvenile Exhibit - Loan Agreement, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 11)
  - Juvenile Exhbibit - Schedule, 2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 12)
  - Manuscript of Susannah Sheffer's Book, Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 13)
  - Media Coverage Report and Clip Pack, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 14)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Book, Undated (Zip-disk 5)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Booklet, etc. - 3rd Edition, Undated (Zip-disk 6)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Press Scrapbook, 1992; 1994-1998; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 15)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Spring 1999 Newsletter, 1999 Spring (Floppy-disk 30)
  - Murder Victim's Families for Reconciliation Stickers, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 16)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Press Scrapbook, 1993 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Murder Victim's Families for Reconciliation T-Shirts, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 17)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Video, Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Journey of Hope, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Journey of Hope, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation and Members, 1996-2002 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation and Members, 2001; 2003 (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
  - "Not In Out Name" - Booklet, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 21)
  - "Not In Our Name" - Booklet, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 22)
  - "Not In Our Name" - 4th Edition Photos, Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 23)
  - "Not In Our Name" - Exhibit List of Damages, 2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 24)
  - "Not In Our Name" - Exhibit Loan Agreement, 2003-2004 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 25)
  - "Not In Our Name" - Exhibit Schedule, 2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 26)
  - "Not In Our Name" - Instructions for Care and Display, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 27)
  - "Not In Our Name" - Photos, 2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 28)
  - Open a Door Project Proposal, 2003; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 29)
  - Peace Studies, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 30)
  - Press Photos, 2002; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 31)
  - Raising Our Voices, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 32)
  - Revisions - New File (August 9th), 2002 (Floppy-disk 31)
  - September 11th OP ED Piece, 2002; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 33)
  - Speeches - Renny Cushing, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 34)
  - "Too Flawed to Fix: The Illinois Death Penalty Experience", Undated (Vhs 2)
  - "Too Flawed to Fix: The Illinois Death Penalty Experience" - Second Edition, Undated (Dvd 2)
  - Unified Abolition Strategy, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 35)
  - Unified Abolition Strategy, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 36)
  - Victim Advocate Feature - Photo, Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 37)
  - Victims' Rights Amendment - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Statement, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 38)
  - Virginia Journey of Hope - Press Clippings Scrapbook, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 39)
  - The Voice, 1992 (Oversized 1, Folder 9)
  - The Voice, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 40)
  - The Voice, 1997-2003 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 41)
  - The Voice, 2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 42)
  - Winter Fundraising Letter, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Outreach and Publications), Folder 43)
- Events, 1992-2003, Undated; 4; 3 cubic ft.
  Series 4 covers events that Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation either attended or organized. Of the events that Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation organized, many have materials that not only outline what took place at the event but the planning and outreach that went into setting it up. Not all events are this extensively covered. Some events are sparsely documented, sometimes with only a single pamphlet or photo, and mainly show Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation's attendance at the event. Included in this series are information packets, memorabilia, pamphlets, programs, pins, photographs, flyers, newspaper clippings, handwritten notes, drafts, correspondence, memos, mailing lists, schedules, checklists, worksheets, evaluation forms, applications, financial summaries, contracts, floppy disks, and vhs tapes.
  - Amnesty International General Meeting - Mid-Atlantic Regonal Conference, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 1)
  - Amnesty International Training - Atlanta, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 2)
  - Amnesty International USA - National Weekend of Faith in Action on the Death Penalty, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 3)
  - Bishop, Illinois - Illinois Moratorium Anniversary, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 4)
  - Brown University - Murder! Should We Seek Vengeance or mercy? Event, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 5)
  - Call to Action - Spring Conference, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 6)
  - Cathedral Hill Hotel San Francisco Event, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 7)
  - Dead Man Walking, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 8)
  - Dead Man Walking - Auction Bids [Restricted], 1998 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 9)
  - Dead Man Walking - Budget, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 10)
  - Dead Man Walking - Deal Memos, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 11)
  - Dead Man Walking - Fact Sheet, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 12)
  - Dead Man Walking - Finances, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 13)
  - Dead Man Walking - Financial Summaries, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 14)
  - Dead Man Walking - General Tickets [Restricted], 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 15)
  - Dead Man Walking - Media Kit, 1995; 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 16)
  - Dead Man Walking - Media Plan, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 17)
  - Dead Man Walking - Merchandise Sale Signs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 18)
  - Dead Man Walking - Pamphlets, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 19)
  - Dead Man Walking - Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 20)
  - Dead Man Walking - Producer Agreement, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 21)
  - Dead Man Walking - Piblicity and Discussion, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 22)
  - Dead Man Walking - Reception Tickets, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 23)
  - Dead Man Walking - Royalties, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 24)
  - Dead Man Walking - Shrine Auditorium Contract, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 25)
  - Dead Man Walking - Signs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 26)
  - Dead Man Walking - Thank Yous and Credits, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 27)
  - Death Penalty Abolition Leadership Meeting, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 28)
  - Death Penalty Debate, 2003; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 29)
  - Death Penalty Focus Tenth Annual Awards Dinner, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 30)
  - Death Sentence: An Interfaith Forum for Humanity, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 31)
  - G-12 Death Penalty Working Group, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 32)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Arun Gandhi Speaking Engagement Contract, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 33)
  - Healing Wounds of Murder-Attendence Scholarship, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 34)
  - Healing Wounds of Murder-Travel Intineraries, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 35)
  - Healing Wounds of Murder-Ben and Jerry's Foundation Grant, 2000; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 36)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Boston College Welcome Letter, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 37)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Bibliography, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 38)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Brochure, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 39)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Call to Action, 1999; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 40)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Catholic Campaign for Human Development Grant, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 41)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Conference Evaluations, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 42)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Credit Card Charges, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 43)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Documentary, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 44)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Donation Thank You List and Letter, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 45)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Draft of Letter, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 46)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Emailed Event Evaluations, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 47)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Evaluations from Social Workers, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 48)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Finances [Restricted], 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 49)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Flyer, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 50)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - General Grant Proposal, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 51)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Housing Arrangements [Restricted], 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 52)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Housing Arrangements, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 10)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Interest Survey, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 53)